The world of Beyonders.
Humanity through consuming potions
harnessed various Beyonder abilities,
completing their promotion to life's natural order.
These twenty-two paths of advancement
start from Sequence 9.
The lower the Sequence number,
the greater the Beyonder abilities.
High-Sequence Beyonders
can possess power comparable to gods.
This path of evolution is called
the Path of the Divine.
Leave!
The evil descended body can't stand the provokation of the Saint's ashes!
It's about to be born!
Can't hold her anymore,
Captain!
Megose mutated,
the evil descended body will be born very soon!
[In Hermes]
As if in a weary dream,
You want to kill my child!
She's gone!
[In Hermes]
Illusion.
Leonard!
Blood Vessel Thief!
It suits me.
No good,
she's too fast!
I can't lock on.
尽全力引向纪念碑大殿
那里是唯一的机会
[In Hermes]
I pray for the power of the Evernight.
I pray for the power of the crimson.
[In Hermes]
I pray for the Goddess' loving grace.
I pray for you to let this evil descended body and "His" vessel slow to a crawl!
[In Hermes]
Submit!
Steal!
Don't think of harming my child!
I'll go seal "Him" first.
After ten seconds,
you two come out again.
Captain!
Silently count to ten.
That's an order.
You don't need to worry.
We are guarding Tingen.
They
are fighting side by side with me.
Ten.
I just want to keep this child!
Nine.
Why?
Must you force me?
Six.
[In Hermes]
As if in a weary dream,
like the shore beyond, and in the grave!
Five.
Four.
Three!
You have to die!
One!
[In Hermes]
Light!
It's over!
[In Hermes]
Submit!
Leave!
Quickly leave!
Faster!
Leave this place!
Hold on!
You―—
Evernight HQ?
You're finally here!
Old man...
Leonard!
Nightmare.
A chance!
This is...
What's going on?
To be honest...
as much as I hate other people who become Beyonders
I respect the Nighthawks just as much.
Must not...
let "Him" be born...
absolutely...
must not..!
Captain...
[In Hermes]
Nightmare.
Klein.
[In Hermes]
Light!
Captain!
We―—
We did it!
We did it.
Klein.
We...
saved Tingen.
Daly...
Captain!
Captain...
Who...
is it?
终于出来了
久违的自由
Ince Zangwill.
将我请出查尼斯门的凡人
他渴望得到
廷根市的圣塞琳娜骨灰
恳求我的凡人
总有一些见不得光的小愿望
这不算什么
一场黑占卜后
存者克莱恩·莫雷蒂在安提哥努斯家族笔记驱
将它送到了瑞尔·比伯家里
这是一个符合逻辑的巧合
之后
克莱恩开枪自杀
令人不解的是
克莱恩并没有死
他成功地活下来
还加入了值夜者
有趣
克莱恩居然能活着
还干掉了序列七的密修会成员
因斯很恼怒
还好结果没有偏离预期
邓恩·史密斯的灵性
受到了巨大的伤害
当然
早在真实造物者降临仪式上
这位神灵
就看出了事情的巧合
不过
希望突破封锁的“祂”
没有拒绝
真是让人难以置信啊
莱恩·莫雷蒂察觉到了因斯·赞格威尔暗中的影
还帮邓恩
掌握了扮演法
不
因斯并不相信
他改变了原来的计划
自责的邓恩
按照惯例服食了科恩黎遗留的非凡特性
扮演消化的进程
被打断
他在关键时刻
做出了错误的判断
将圣赛琳娜的骨灰
带出了查尼斯门
你杀了克莱恩·莫雷蒂这个总是让他计划出现
以剩余的死神后裔特性布置仪式
服食下圣赛琳娜的骨灰
成功从死神途径的序列五看门人
晋升为黑夜途径的序列四守夜人
成为
Demigod.
太阳依旧照耀大地
廷根市几乎所有人都没有察觉到
他们幸运地躲过了一场巨大的灾难
Tingen's story
ends here.
队长和克莱恩
一封还没译码的电报
应该是之前圣堂发来的
总部已经知道真凶是谁了
红手套在追查
申请加入红手套
需要什么
打听到了
说是有个凶恶的罪犯潜入到了廷根
但幸好
警察部门已经阻止了这场危机
女神保佑
所以克莱恩今天早上才精神恍惚
压力很大的样子
克莱恩在警局是历史顾问
又不管抓罪犯
我们一向节俭的梅丽莎居然肯舍得买五苏勒
原来是想让克莱恩放松高兴啊
Klein,
你回
绯红的满月升起
映着大地
生命的火焰短暂
身躯终归尘土
英雄的魂灵永恒
是不熄灭的灯火
是划破劫难的荆棘
是唱给罪恶的挽歌
愿不羁的风
引你前往女神的神国
愿长夜繁星闪烁
愿你回归最初的纯净
唯一的归宿是安宁
唯一的归宿
是安宁
很抱漱
我没能及时赶到
但幕后之人
我应该知道是谁了
霍纳奇斯
这算是陪葬品了吧
我现在
是什么呢
或许
只是一个从地狱爬出来
想要复仇的恶灵吧
因斯
赞格威尔
那些巧合
就是封印物0-08的能力
写下的事情注定会实现
不
应该有一定的限制
因斯的目的是拿到圣赛琳娜的骨灰
那他针对的目标并不是我
而是
Captain.
因斯·赞格威尔目前所在的城市
兰尔乌斯的位置
我变强大的希望
贝克兰德
We―—
saved Tingen.
塞维亚菊
象征着快乐
熟悉的街巷人来人往
原谅我这次走得匆忙
究竟要蜕多少副皮囊
才能让愿望不落空想
[In Hermes]
Light!
刺破虚妄
别来无恙
脱不下
半身伪装
另一个我
名存实亡
别害恒
会抵达
别停下
就盛开吧
向阳的花
你可记得我吗
会记得我吗
先生
请问您是
夏洛克
莫里亚蒂